John and Ginny Dildine collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Sound Recordings
  - AFC 1975/001: SR108 (2), Recorded: unknown, RXG 0778; 1:33
    This appears to be the recording of a telephone conversation between a man and a woman. They are trying to schedule something.
    Start Conversation
    16:11 "The Crawdad Song"
  - AFC 1975/001: SR108 (3), Recorded: unknown, RXG 0778; 15:01
    This is a continuation of SR108 (1). It appears to be the making of a demo of two (unidentified) women singers with banjo, guitar and bass. An unidentified male singer is also on several songs. This session is continued on SR109.
    Start Tuning
    0:42 "Ridin' in a buggy"
    2:11 laughter
    2:23 "Cindy"
    7:02 Talking
    7:40 "Old Joe Clark"
    11:00 Laughter
    11:15 "Brandy Leave Me Alone"
    13:03 Talking, laughter and tuning
    13:47 Fragment of an unidentified song.
    14:52 Talking.
  - AFC 1975/001: SR109, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0779; 29:45
    This is a continuation of SR108 (1) and SR108 (3). It appears to be the making of a demo of two (unidentified) women singers with banjo, guitar and bass. An unidentified male singer is also on several songs. A previously used tape was used for this session, so in several places the original recordings are briefly heard.
    Start A big band is heard briefly
    0:31 "Fare ye Well My Own True Love" (take 1)
    3:20 "Fare ye Well My Own True Love" (take 2)
    6:08 Talking
    6:33 "Fare ye Well My Own True Love" (take 3)
    8:10 "Fare ye Well My Own True Love" (take 4)
    10:30 Talking, laughing and preparation for the next song
    11:23 First line: "If he's gone let him go, let him sink or let him swim"
    13:48 Talking
    14:01 "Ain't Gonna Work Tomorrow"
    16:45 Talking
    16:58 "Doney Gal" (take 1)
    19:42 Talking
    20:03 "Doney Gal" (take 2)
    23:47 talking
    24:24 "You Are My Sunshine" (take 1)
    25:12 Laughter
    25:30 "You Are My Sunshine" (take 2)
    28:10 Big Band music and the sign off of a radio broadcast called "Pipeline"
  - AFC 1975/001: SR111, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0780; 14:01
    This recording seems to be a set of dubs of political songs from phonograph records. There are several male performers. Several of the songs have Canadian themes.
    Start "This Land is our Land" [Canadian Version] performer 1, banjo
    2:26 "Brand New Democratic Party Train" performer #1, banjo
    5:41 first line: "A Douglas for me, a Douglas for me, if you're not a Douglas you're no use to me" performer #2, guitar
    6:50 Repeat of previous song
    8:05 ["We Are Building a New Party"] [to the tune of "Jacob's Ladder"] performer #3, guitar
    9:49 "We Shall Not Be Moved" performer, guitar
    11:57 "Solidarity Forever" performer, guitar
    14:01 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR0112, Recorded: undated, RAA 54540; [no tape log is available for this item]
    [Tape box is labeled "Skip James interview."]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR113, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0781; 17:41
    This is a recording of six songs by an unidentified male singer and his guitar. There seems to two men doing the recording; neither of them sounds like John Dildine. The guitar is quite clear but the lyrics are difficult to understand. The singer sounds like an older African American.
    Start Talking about the next song.
    0:49 "Drunken Spree" unknown performer, vocal and guitar
    3:20 Talking about the next song.
    4:28 ["Won't You Go Along New?"] unknown performer, vocal and guitar
    6:04 Talking about the next song.
    7:12 Unidentified song. [The singer says the title is a "girl's name." It is something like "Celon."] unknown performer, vocal and guitar
    8:00 Talking about the next song.
    9:17 "All Night Long" (take 1) unknown performer, vocal and guitar
    10:34 Talking about the next song.
    10:52 "All Night Long" (take 2) unknown performer, vocal and guitar
    14:00 Talking about the next song.
    14:38 "All Night Long" (take 3) unknown performer, vocal and guitar
    17:41 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR0114, Recorded: undated, RAA 54541; [no tape log is available for this item]
    [from original inventory, this is likely part of the "Skip James interview."]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR0115, Recorded: undated, RAA 54542; [no tape log is available for this item]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR0116, Recorded: undated, RAA 54543; [no tape log is available for this item]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR0117, Recorded: undated, RAA 54544; [no tape log is available for this item]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR0118, Recorded: undated, RAA 54545; [no tape log is available for this item]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR0119, Recorded: undated, RAA 54546; [no tape log is available for this item]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR120, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0782; 12:11
    This appears to be a recording session of an unidentified blues singer-guitar player.
    Start Discussion of the recording of the next song.
    1:32 Guitar picking in preparation for the next song.
    2:10 "Catfish Blues" - start
    2:40 Getting ready for take.
    2:47 "Catfish Blues" (take 1)
    4:27 Discussion about another take.
    4:49 "Catfish Blues" (take 2)
    6:33 Getting ready for the next song.
    8:02 "Bad, Bad Whiskey" (take 1)
    9:50 Talking
    10:02 "Bad, Bad Whiskey" (take 2)
    11:01 Talking about the next song.
    11:50 "Black Girl"
    10:52 "All Night Long" (take 2)
  - AFC 1975/001: SR121, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0783; 11:51
    In this recording an unidentified man reads a poem, 3 takes, then records a message to two raging seas"
    Start "The Wall" (take 1)
    3:35 "The Wall" (take 2)
    6:50 "The Wall" (take 3)
    10:18 The reader records a message to John Dildine.
  - AFC 1975/001: SR122, Recorded: undated, RXG 0820; [no tape log is available for this item]
    [the tape box indicates this may be "The Music of Kenya, British Information Services tape recording." ]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR123, Recorded: probably 1961, RXG 0784; 28:14
    This is a recording of Peter Weston interviewing Jim Kweskin. Kweskin also sings and plays guitar. The recording session is continued on SR124. The recording was made in the home of Peter and Judy Weston in St. Louis, MO.
    Start Peter Weston talking with Jim Kweskin).
    2:18 "You're No Good" (a Jesse Fuller song) Kweskin, vocal and guitar
    3:55 Weston and Kweskin talk about "San Francisco Bay Blues" and Jesse Fuller's records. They talk about the next song.
    6:49 "The Cuckoo" Kweskin, vocal and guitar
    9:47 Weston and Kweskin talk about where Kweskin collects material.
    11:45 "House of David Blues" Kweskin, vocal and guitar
    14:12 Weston and Kweskin talk about the previous song.
    16:00 blank
    16:24 Recording resumes. Kweskin talks about the guitar tuning for the next song.
    17:00 "Buffalo Skinners" Kweskin, vocal and guitar
    21:38 Weston and Kweskin discuss the previous song. They discuss guitar tuning.
    23:26 "Cherry Red" Kweskin, vocal and guitar
    26:20 Weston and Kweskin talk about blues and other genres Kweskin plays. They talk about Kweskin playing the banjo.
    28:19 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR124, Recorded: probably 1961, RXG 0785; 30:42
    This is a recording of Peter Weston interviewing Jim Kweskin. Kweskin also sings and plays guitar. The recording session began on SR123. The recording was made in the home of Peter and Judy Weston in St. Louis, MO.
    Start The next song is introduced
    1:16 "Days of ‘49" Kweskin, vocal and guitar
    5:20 Weston and Kweskin talk about Mississippi John Hurt. Weston asks Kweskin to play Hurt's song "Frankie."
    7:18 "Frankie" Kweskin, vocal and guitar
    10:00 Weston and Kweskin discuss the previous song and the next song.
    10:59 "Stagolee" Kweskin, vocal and guitar
    13:50 Weston and Kweskin talk about Kweskin's upcoming travel to Europe. Weston closed the recording.
    15:05 This 15 minute segment is Weston sending a message to John Dildine about the Kweskin recording and what's going on in the music scene in St. Louis. He talks about why he's made this recording. He says that the club called the Laughing Buddha has burned down. He talks about a newly opened coffee shop which offers live music. He mentions Robin and Ellen Christenson, who are on other recordings in this collection. He mentions Jean Redpath, Odetta, and the Weavers playing in St. Louis. Judy Weston walks in and talks.
    30:42 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR125, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0786; 12:38
    This SR seems to be dubs of an unidentified Bluegrass Band.
  - AFC 1975/001: SR126, Recorded: ca. 1959-01, RXG 0787; 30:52
    This is the second part of a recording of a John Dildine radio broadcast with The New Lost City Ramblers: John Cohen, Mike Seeger and Tom Paley. The first part is on SR127.
    Start Dildine talks about magazines devoted to folk music including "Caravan" and "Sing Out!" He tells listener how to subscribe to "Sing Out!"
    1:37 "Farewell to Tarwathie" (recorded) A.L. Lloyd and Ewan MacColl
    4:07 Dildine and John Cohen talk.
    5:02 "Charlie Was a Good Old Man" John Cohen, banjo solo
    5:45 Cohen talks about the previous song and the next song.
    6:14 "You Are My Sunshine" John Cohen, banjo solo
    6:42 Dildine and Cohen talk about banjo tunings. Mike Seeger joins them.
    7:53 "Foggy Mountain Breakdown" The NLCR
    8:34 Dildine and The NLCR talk about bluegrass music and a bluegrass record that Seeger has just made. Seeger talks about the evolution of old time music into bluegrass. He mentions Jimmy Driftwood.
    16:04 "Chewing Gum" The NLCR
    17:53 Dildine and The NLCR talk about the previous song. Seeger says it came from a Carter Family recording. Tom Paley tunes his guitar.
    19:10 "Buckdancers Choice" Paley, guitar solo
    20:08 Getting ready for the next song.
    21:13 "The wreck of the Tennessee Gravy Train" (an Uncle Dave Macon song) The NLCR
    24:19 Dildine asks for one more song. He and Cohen talk about the folk song magazines "Caravan" and Sing Out!"
    26:11 "Sally Goodin" The NLCR
    27:30 Dildine closes the broadcast.
    28:14 "Railroad Bill" (recorded) theme song
  - AFC 1975/001: SR127, Recorded: ca. 1959-01, RXG 0788; 26:02
    This is the first part of a recording of a John Dildine radio broadcast with The New Lost City Ramblers: John Cohen, Mike Seeger and Tom Paley. The second part is on SR126.
    Start Opening theme, "Railroad Bill" recorded. Dildine introduces the program, a live session with the New Lost City Ramblers: John Cohen, Mike Seeger and Tom Paley. Dildine introduces the first song.
    3:14 "Old Joe Clark," recorded Jimmy Driftwood
    4:52 Dildine introduces the New Lost City Ramblers. He says this is 8 months since their first program (May, 1958).
    5:56 "Forked Dear" The NLCR
    6:48 Dildine and the NLCR talk about learning songs from old phonograph records, and other things.
    9:32 "Beware, Young Ladies" The NLCR
    11:57 they talk about the previous song and other songs from the Depression Era. They talk about folk music publications. They talk about Alan Lomax and an article in "Sing Out!"
    15:30 "Leaving Home" (an unusual version of "Frankie and Johnny") The NLCR
    18:32 Dildine and the NLCR talk about tuning their instruments.
    20:17 While the NLCR are tuning, Dildine plays two recorded songs by A.L. Lloyd and Ewan MacColl, "Sperm Whale Fishing" and "Blood Red Roses." Also on the record are Peggy Seeger playing banjo and John Cohen playing harmonica.
    25:37 Dildine talks about the previous songs.
    26:02 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR128, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0789; 32:15
    This seems to be a copy, i.e. dub, of a record album of an unidentified male singer. On most songs he sings and plays guitar. However, the last song is a banjo solo.
    Start "Boll Weevil" vocal, guitar
    3:44 "Devilish Mary" vocal, guitar
    5:45 "The Devil and the Farmer's Wife" vocal, guitar
    9:23 "Red Apple Juice" vocal, guitar
    11:57 "Tom Cat Blues" vocal, guitar
    14:32 "Way Down Town" or "A Dollar is All I Crave" vocal, guitar
    18:00 "Seven Drunken Nights" also known as "Cabbage Head" also known as "You Old Fool vocal, guitar"
    21:29 Unidentified banjo solo by the unidentified performer.
  - AFC 1975/001: SR129, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0790; 24:42
    This is a set of blues songs by an unidentified male singer. He plays guitar on all the songs.
    Start "Motherless Children" vocal, guitar
    4:24 unidentified blues song vocal, guitar
    10:04 ["Keys to the Highway"] vocal, guitar
    14:27 "Frankie and Albert" take 2 vocal, guitar
    18:48 "Keep on Truckin' Mama" take 1 vocal, guitar
    23:09 "Fare thee Well" or "Dink's Song" vocal, guitar
    24:42 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR130, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0791; 21:01
    This is a set of blues and gospel songs by an unidentified male singer. He plays guitar on all the songs. On some of the songs someone plays harmonica.
    Start "Lose Your Money (But don't Lose your Mind" vocal, guitar
    02:46 unidentified blues song vocal, guitar
    04:45 ["Ain't That A Rockin'] the first line is "Now Moses was a little baby born in Egypt land" vocal, guitar, harmonica
    07:38 "Oh, Mary Don't You Weep" vocal, guitar, harmonica
    10:30 "Careless Love" vocal, guitar, harmonica
    13:59 chorus: "Sorry to hear …. That's the Way It Goes " vocal, guitar
    16:30 "James Alley Blues" vocal, guitar
    21:01 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR131, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0792; 34:02
    This is a set of blues and gospel songs by an unidentified male singer.
    Start "Gravel" vocal, harmonica
    03:22 "My Bonnie Lies over the Ocean" vocal, guitar
    06:30 "Poor Man but a Good Man" vocal, guitar
    08:44 "Stagolee" vocal, guitar
    12:51 "Noted Rider," take 1 vocal, guitar
    15:25 "I'd Rather Drink Muddy Water" ["I Know You Rider"] vocal, guitar
    17:32 "Twelve Gates to the City" vocal, guitar
    18:57 unidentified song(s) harmonica solo(s)
    22:35 first line "I don't know what you've been doin'" vocal, harmonica, guitar
    24:10 [Bottle Up and Go"] vocal, harmonica, guitar
    26:48 first line "Your mama don't allow you to stay out all night long" vocal, harmonica, guitar
    29:50 "Keys to the Highway" vocal, guitar
    34:02 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR132, Recorded: unknown [probably late 1950s], RXG 0793; 28:23
    This is a recording of the second part of a John Dildine radio broadcast. In the first part (not taped) Dildine played recordings of Leadbelly. In this part his guest is Dave Sears who sings and plays banjo.
    Start Dildine introduces the program and Dave Sears.
    00:40 Sears talks about the next song.
    01:13 "Ox Driving Song" vocal and banjo
    04:20 Dildine and Sears talk about using a barbeque grill at home.
    06:09 "Dunderbeck's Machine" vocal and banjo
    07:59 Dildine and Sears talk about children's songs.
    09:08 "Ha Ha This-a-Way" vocal and banjo
    11:16 Dildine and Sears talk about a Leadbelly Christmas song.
    11:28 "Christmas is Coming (It's Almost Day)" vocal and banjo
    12:06 Dildine and Sears discuss the previous song and the next song.
    13:00 "On a Monday" vocal and banjo
    15:10 Dildine does a station break.
    16:28 Dildine and Sears talk about the next song.
    17:33 "Roll On Columbia Roll On" vocal and banjo
    21:18 Dildine and Sears talk about Woody Guthrie and the previous song.
    22:12 "John Henry" vocal and banjo
    25:50 Dildine thanks Dave Sears. Closing theme, "Railroad Bill." Dildine closes the program.
    28:07 End of program
    28:32 End of recording
  - AFC 1975/001: SR133, Recorded: undated, RXG 0821; [no tape log is available for this item]
    [per the orginal inventory this may be "Tape of old 78 records found in St. Louis." ]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR134, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0794; 14:15
    This appears to be "demo" recordings of several songs by two unidentified male performers.
    0:39 "UAW" (Take 1) vocal, banjo and guitar
    2:34 blank
    2:47 "UAW" (Take 2) vocal, banjo and guitar
    5:12 "UAW" chorus only vocal, banjo and guitar
    5:43 "UAW" chorus only vocal, banjo and guitar
    6:00 Dildine and performers doing sound set up and sound check.
    7:45 "UAW" (Take 3) vocal, banjo and guitar
    10:06 false starts
    10:40 "Solidarity" (Take 1) vocal, banjo
    11:27 "Solidarity" (Take 2) vocal and banjo
    12:15 talking
    12:35 "No Irish Need Apply" vocal, guitar
    14:15 END
  - AFC 1975/001: SR135, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0795; 16:01
    This is a John Dildine tape of recorded music.
    Start Dildine talks about songs and singing. He talks about the Archive of Folk Music at the Library of Congress. Native American music is playing in the background.]
    3:02 An unidentified Sioux mother singing her child to sleep.
    4:12 Dildine talks about the Mormon migration to Utah.
    5:04 "The Handcart Song" introduces this traditional Mormon song [then sings it a capella.] An unidentified man
    8:21 Dildine talks about the next song.
    9:58 "Streets of Laredo" an unaccompanied man, a capella
    11:50 Dildine introduces the next song.
    12:17 A lament for the dead unidentified Sioux singing, flute [which may really be part of the next song]
    13:12 Dildine introduces the next song.
    13:42 A Sioux courting song unidentified man, flute and vocal
    16:01 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR136 (1), Recorded: ca. 1963, RXG 0796; 35:42
    This is the first part of a spoken letter that Peter and Judy Weston are sending to John and Ginny Dildine.
    Start "Green Green Rocky Road" Dave Van Ronk, vocal and guitar
    3:47 Peter Weston introduces the next song. [He attributes it to the Reverend Gary Davis. My research attributes it to Davis and to Blind Boy Fuller, 1936.]
    4:28 "Baby Let Me Lay It On You" Dave Van Ronk, vocal and guitar
    5:57 Peter and Judy Weston talk to the Dildines [via this tape recording]. They talk about [among other things] folk musicians, folk clubs, children, summer vacation, and their careers.
    35:42 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR136 (2), Recorded: ca. 1963, RXG 0796; 35:37
    This is the second part of a (spoken) letter that Peter and Judy Weston are sending to John and Ginny Dildine.
    Start Judy Weston talks about the songs she is going to sing and the books from which she learned the songs.
    2:56 "The Orange and Blue" Judy Weston, vocal, guitar
    4:39 "Georgie" Judy Weston, vocal, guitar
    6:58 "Gypsy Davy" Judy Weston, vocal, banjo
    9:40 unidentified song, written by Judy Weston Judy Weston, vocal, banjo
    11:30 Judy Weston talks about the previous song.
    14:15 The Westons talk to the Dildines: Tom Paley, young performers; a book by John Updike; a Howie Mitchell record; they ask the Dildines to visit them; the Newport Folk Festival; Mississippi John Hurt; Dave Van Ronk; Judy plays banjo in the background.
    32:33 Unidentified recorded music.
    35:37 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR137, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0797; 16:26
    This seems to be a demo tape of an unidentified male performer.
    Start unidentified song vocal, banjo
    0:38 Talking, banjo tuning, etc.
    1:56 ["James A, Garfield"] vocal, banjo
    9:18 Conversation about the next song.
    10:14 "The Wagoner's Lad" vocal, banjo
    13:32 Conversation about the next song.
    13:47 "The cuckoo" vocal, banjo
    16:26 End of recording before the song is finished.
  - AFC 1975/001: SR138, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0798; 30:22
    This is a mix of several male performers. None are identified.
    Start No recording
    0:27 "Henry Lee" vocal, banjo
    3:29 "The Lonesome Road" vocal, banjo
    6:05 segment of an unidentified song vocal with band
    7:00 "Stagolee" vocal with band
    10:41 "Frankie and Albert" vocal with band
    17:34 "Duncan and Brady" vocal, guitar
    19:16 unidentified song banjo solo
    19:50 unidentified song vocal, banjo
    24:09 ["James A. Garfield"] vocal, banjo
    30:22 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR139, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0799; 30:02
    This is an instrumental set of guitar solos played in several different styles. Neither the performer(s) nor the songs are identified.
    Start unidentified guitar solo
    3:20 unidentified guitar solo
    6:06 unidentified guitar solo
    10:24 unidentified guitar solo
    12:54 unidentified guitar solo
    15:43 unidentified guitar solo
    18:27 ["The House of the Rising Sun"] guitar solo
    20:40 variations on "The Battle Hymn of the Republic" guitar solo
    25:27 conversation
    25:45 variations on "Pomp and Circumstance" by Edward Elgar guitar solo
    28:25 no recording
    28:42 [The end of a radio broadcast "Pipeline." The DJ is Jim [Toehill]. [Dildine probably recorded the guitar player(s) over previously recorded tape.]
  - AFC 1975/001: SR140, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0800; 21:31
    Except for the first song, this is an instrumental set of guitar solos played in several different styles. The first song has lap-dulcimer and guitar. Neither the performer(s) nor the songs are identified.
    Start unidentified instrumental, dulcimer and guitar
    3:29 unidentified guitar solo
    5:37 unidentified guitar solo
    10:05 unidentified guitar solo
    12:50 variations on "Cripple Creek" guitar solo
    14:43 unidentified guitar solo
    18:20 unidentified guitar solo
    21:31 End
  - AFC 1975/001: SR141, Recorded: unknown, RXG 0801; 31:18
    On the first part of this tape John Dildine interviews Pat Webb. Mr. Webb plays several guitar solos. On the second part of this take John Dildine interviews John Michelin who plays and sings several songs.
  - AFC 1975/001: SR142, Recorded: 1964, RXG 0802; 29:52
    There are two parts to this John Dildine tape. The first centers on the Reverend Robert Wilkins; the second on Bob and Evelyn Beers. There is no indication that this is a radio broadcast. See also SR075 and SR076 for additional Wilkins' material. See also SR030, SR031, SR044 and SR088 for additional Bob Beers' material.
    Start unidentified guitar solo, Pat Webb
    3:17 John Dildine introduces and interviews Pat Webb. They talk about Webb's musical background. He's been touring with Charlotte Daniels.
    5:30 [slow blues] guitar solo, Pat Webb
    9:56 Dildine and Webb discuss how Webb learned to play guitar. Webb also plays mandolin. They discuss Webb's playing style and performing plans.
    14:10 "The White Stallion" guitar solo, Pat Webb
    18:13 CUT!
    18:23 Dildine interviews John [Michelin] of St. Louis. MO.
    20:10 "Old Blue" guitar and vocal, John [Michelin]
    23:16 Dildine and [Michelin] discuss [Michelin's] musical background.
    27:48 "Abilene" [Michelin credits this song to Bob Gibson] guitar and vocal, John [Michelin]
    30:03 End of recording
    31:18 End
    Start Dildine talks about folk music. He introduces the music of Reverend Robert Wilkins.
    1:20 Wilkins talks about being a blues player then becoming a church goer.
    1:50 "Nashville Stonewall Blues" (commercial recording) Robert Wilkins, guitar
    3:12 "Do Lord" (recorded in Washington, D.C., in 1964) Reverend Robert Wilkins, guitar
    6:01 Dildine introduces and interview he had with Reverend Wilkins on February 18, 1964.
    6:36 Dildine interviews Reverend Wilkins. They discuss Wilkins's early recordings. Wilkin's says he's not played blues since 1936, only sacred songs. They talk about when Wilkins began playing music. He was drafted into the Army in WWI. They talk about sacred songs that Wilkins is playing now. Dildine asks how Wilkins feels about being recognized for his (long ago) blues playing.
    19:20 Dildine introduces Bob "Fiddler" Beers.
    19:38 An unidentified Sioux fiddle tune Bob Beers, fiddle and Evelyn Beers, straw beating
    20:52 Dildine and the Beers talk about the previous song.
    24:20 "The [???] Rambles" Bob Beers, fiddle and Evelyn Beers, straw beating
    25:17 Dildine asks Bob Beers how he got started playing the fiddle. They talk about the psaltery.
    28:30 "Johnnie Came A' Courtin'" Bob Beers, psaltery and Evelyn Beers, vocal